Guide to the C&U Poster Advertising Company Records, 1896-2004 and undated RL.11125
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Organizations, 1896-2004 and undated; 5
  - OAAA (Outdoor Advertising Association of America), 1946-1999 and undated; 8
    - 1912-1952 Federal Litigation (Box 50)
    - Articles and reports, 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Condemnation seminar, 1995; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Confidential Bulletin, 1947-1948 (Box 50)
    - Constitution and By-laws, 1959 (Box 50)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1997; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Dues, 1989-1995 (Box 51)
    - Executive Committee, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Fairleigh-Dickinson/Duke (OAAA Archives), 1981-1997 (Box 51)
    - First Medium, 1975 (Box 51)
    - Highway Beautification Act Primer, 1992 (Box 51)
    - Highway Beautification legislation, 1965 (Box 51)
    - Historical documents, 1946 and undated (Box 51)
    - Independent Advertising Council (formerly Small Advertising Council), 1986-1989 (Box 51)
    - Industry financial survey, 1996 (Box 51)
    - Institute of Outdoor Advertising (IOA) reports, 1980-1981 (Box 51)
    - ISTEA (Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act), 1992 (Box 51)
    - Ladue vs. Gilleo, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Legal Forum, 1992; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Legal Forum, 1996; 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Legislative Forum, 1980 (Box 52)
    - Main file, 1991-1996; 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Notre Dame Outdoor Advertising School, 1948 (Box 52)
    - OASA (Outdoor Advertising Suppliers Association) News, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Opposition strategy handouts, undated (Box 52)
    - Outlook newsletter, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Reports, 1995-1999 (Box 53)
    - Salary survey, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Transcript regarding Prismavision not being a moving sign, 1987 (Box 53)
  - OAAII (Outdoor Advertising Association of Illinois, Inc.), 1896-2004 and undated; 9
    - 100th anniversary, 1995-1996; 4 folders (Box 53)
    - Adams vs. Virginia Beach, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Annual Meeting, Buckle Up campaign, 1992-1993 (Box 53)
    - Company profiles, 1995 (Box 53)
    - Constitution and By-laws, 1959 (Box 53)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1964 (Box 53)
    - Covers of documents taken to 100th anniversary meeting, undated (Box 53)
    - Dingeman vs. Mount Zion, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Dingeman vs. Mount Zion, 1987 (Box 54)
    - Dingeman vs. Saginaw, 1980 (Box 54)
    - Documents, 1953-1964 (Box 54)
    - Dolson vs. City of Macomb, 1976-1977 (Box 54)
    - Economic Values of On-Premise Signs (Raymond T. Anderson, National Electric Sign Association), 1983 (Box 54)
    - Excerpts from the Bill Poster magazine, 1896-1930; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Foster & Kleiser vs. DuPage, 1981 (Box 54)
    - HACA--Land acquisition, 1982-1990 (Box 54)
    - HACA--Poster panels, 1975-1978 (Box 54)
    - HACA--Proposed administrative code, 1997-1998 (Box 55)
    - HACA--Rule changes, 1992-1993 (Box 55)
    - HACA--Rules, 1983 (Box 55)
    - HACA--Rules for Billboards near Federal Highways (IDOT), 1976 (Box 55)
    - HACA--Rules for Directional/Official Road Signs (IDOT), 1972 (Box 55)
    - HACA--Signboard Validation (IDOT), 1974-1992 (Box 55)
    - HACA--Sign laws, 1988-1997 (Box 55)
    - Hoopeston Poster Advertising, circa 1910-1915 (Box 55)
    - IDOT (Illinois Department of Transportation)--Excess property, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Key Outdoor vs. Galesburg, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Key Outdoor vs. Galesburg, 2001-2004; 3 folders (Box 56)
    - Legislative information, 1958-1965 (Box 56)
    - Libertyville-Scadron, 1995 (Box 56)
    - Lobbying, 1999; 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Mac-Mar (McClintic-Marshall) Pittsburgh, undated (Box 56)
    - Meeting binder, 1994-1995 (Box 57)
    - Meetings, 1995 (Box 57)
    - Membership, 1952-1956 (Box 57)
    - Membership brochures, 1991-1995 (Box 57)
    - Minutes, 1952-1965 (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous, 1937-1964 (Box 57)
    - National Advertising Co. (3-M) vs. Downer's Grove, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 57)
    - National Advertising Co. (3-M) vs. Downer's Grove, 1987-1988; 4 folders (Box 58)
    - OAAII vs. Downer's Grove, 1987-1988; 4 folders (Box 58)
    - Outdoor Graphics vs. Burlington, 1995 (Box 58)
    - Rate book/Antitrust, 1992 (Box 58)
    - Rate books, 1980-1993 (Box 59)
    - Rep. Ray LaHood fundraiser, 1995 (Box 59)
    - Safety/Membership meeting, 1995 (Box 59)
    - Sales meeting, 1990 (Box 59)
    - Seminar: Selling Outdoor in the 90s (Jonathan Crawford), 1995 (Box 59)
    - Southern Illinois, 1994-1995 (Box 59)
    - Thomas Cusack Company, 1973-1996 (Box 59)
    - Tobacco settlement, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 59)
- Press and Publicity, 1957-2001 and undated; 6
  - General Files, 1957-2001 and undated; 10
    - 603 E. University Avenue, undated (Box 60)
    - Articles about billboards, 1957-2000; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Articles on billboard regulation, 1965-1975 (Box 60)
    - Articles on Bob Pope's county zoning remarks, 1969-1972; 4 folders (Box 60)
    - Articles on Bob Pope's county zoning remarks, 1969-1972 (Box 61)
    - C&U 80th anniversary, 1992 (Box 61)
    - Champaign-Urbana sign ordinances, 1969-1980; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - County zoning, 1971-1972 (Box 61)
    - Editorials favorable on billboards, 1991 and undated (Box 61)
    - League of Women Voters and other organizations, 1966-1982 (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 61)
    - News Gazette, 1982-2001; 4 folders (Box 61)
    - Newspaper clippings on sign ordinances, 1970-1985; 3 folders (Box 62)
- Printed Material, 1930-1998 and undated; 7
  - General Files, 1930-1998 and undated; 11
    - ABA Committee on Condemnation, 1977-1980; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Amortization of Outdoor Advertising Structures (Guy Gelbron and Crane McClennen), 1973 (Box 63)
    - Appraisal of Roadside Advertising Signs (Donald Sutte), 1972 (Box 63)
    - Basics of Licensing, 1988 (Box 63)
    - BOCA Basic Building Code, 1970 (Box 64)
    - Cases on Sign Law (Guy Gelbron) Vol. 1, undated (Box 64)
    - Cases on Sign Law (Guy Gelbron) Vol. 2, undated (Box 65)
    - Champaign Building Codes, 1974 (Box 65)
    - Champaign County Town Meeting, 1977 (Box 65)
    - Champaign Land Use Element, 1979 (Box 65)
    - Champaign New Streets and Subdivisions Ordinance, undated (Box 65)
    - Champaign Zoning Ordinance, 1965 (Box 65)
    - Champaign Zoning Ordinance, 1965 (Box 66)
    - City Signs and Lights (Ashley/Myer/Smith), 1976 (Box 66)
    - Constitutional and Judicial Limits on the Community's Power to Downzone (C. Thomas Williamson), 1980 (Box 66)
    - Greater Champaign-Urbana Invites You, undated (Box 66)
    - Guide for Municipal Zoning Administration (Smith, Forrest, Freund), 1972 (Box 66)
    - Highway Research Board--Control of Highway Advertising Signs, 1971 (Box 66)
    - Hong Kong Sign Book (Constani and Kirkpatrick), 1981 (Box 66)
    - In Support of a Uniform Sign Code (James Claus), 1973 (Box 66)
    - Inventions and Innovations (U.S. Department of Energy), 1985-1991 (Box 66)
    - Inverse Condemnation and Related Government Liability, 1989 (Box 66)
    - Mac-Mar (McClintic-Marshall) Pittsburgh, 1930 (Box 67)
    - Macomb/Western Illinois University, 1991 (Box 67)
    - Mandamus and Inverse Condemnation (Costigan and Neirynck), 1985 (Box 67)
    - Model Sign Control Ordinance (Arthur Rigolo), 1965 (Box 67)
    - NEPRO Uniform Sign Code, 1973 (Box 67)
    - NESA Guideline Standards for On-Premise Signs, 1968 (Box 67)
    - New Product Development (U.S. Department of Energy), 1991 (Box 67)
    - NIOSH Health and Safety Guide for Sign and Advertising Display Manufacturers, 1976 (Box 67)
    - OAAA State Network Directory, 1998 (Box 67)
    - OAAA Summary of Arthur Little's Roadside Study, undated (Box 67)
    - Operation Streetscape (Harold Lewis Malt), 1973 (Box 67)
    - Outdoor Advertising History and Regulation (John Houck), 1969 (Box 67)
    - Patents and Trademarks, 1989-1991 (Box 67)
    - Preparation of an Effective Outdoor Advertising Control Ordinance (George McInturff), undated (Box 67)
    - Regulatory Taking: The Limits of Land Use Controls (Ed. G. Richard Hill), 1990 (Box 68)
    - Rolling Billboards, 1993 (Box 68)
    - Signs of the City (Tom Martinson), 1995 (Box 68)
    - Some Policy Considerations for Sign Legislation (R.J. Claus), 1973 (Box 68)
    - Street Graphics (William Ewald), 1971-1982 (Box 68)
    - Study of Human Response to Visual Environments in Urban Areas (Arthur Little), 1967 (Box 68)
    - The Chief/Waste No Words billboard (Tquajia Noji Groda painted by J. Walter Wilkinson), undated (Box 68)
    - The Outdoor Advertising Control Program Needs to be Reassessed (GAO report), 1985 (Box 68)
    - Tiffin Outdoor Advertising Structures, undated (Box 68)
    - Urbana Zoning Ordinance, 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Articles and presentations on sign ordinances, 1960s-1970s (Box 69)
    - Urbana Zoning Ordinance, 1970-1973 (Box 69)
- Slides and Photographic Materials, 1936-2000 and undated; 8
  - Slides, 1959-1990s and undated; 12
    - Ad Club speech on outdoor advertising in France, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Aesthetics, out of town, bad, etc., undated; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Architectural, undated (Box 70)
    - Consumer behavior, undated (Box 70)
    - Downtown Champaign, undated (Box 70)
    - Europe, 1966; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Florida OAA speech, undated (Box 70)
    - French billboards, undated (Box 70)
    - Kip Pope, undated (Box 70)
    - Locations by street (storage box), undated (Box 71)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1990s; 4 folders (Box 71)
    - Municipal League, undated (Box 71)
    - Numbered locations (storage box), undated; 2 folders (Box 71)
    - OAAA, 1970 (Box 71)
    - Old slides, undated (Box 71)
    - Presentation to Champaign Planning Commission, 1970 (Box 72)
    - Presentation to Urbana Planning Commission, 1969 (Box 72)
    - Seabrook, undated (Box 72)
    - Urban Ordinance Kit, undated (Box 72)
    - Used in slide shows, undated (Box 72)
    - Stereo slides, 1940s (Box 79)
  - Photographs, 1936-2000 and undated; 13
    - 5-PointsUrbana, 1957-1958 (Box 72)
    - 603 E. University Avenue, 1955 (Box 72)
    - Aesthetics, undated; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Aesthetics--Grainger Engineering Library, University of Illinois, undated (Box 72)
    - Alton, trees, 1995 (Box 72)
    - Automobile, undated (Box 72)
    - Banks, undated (Box 72)
    - Billboard art, undated (Box 72)
    - Bob Pope, undated (Box 72)
    - Champaign National Bank, undated (Box 72)
    - Cities' welcome signs, undated (Box 72)
    - Columns, undated; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - Costa Rica, undated (Box 72)
    - Dick's Camera, undated (Box 72)
    - Dingeman, undated (Box 72)
    - Dodson Travel, undated (Box 73)
    - Dumpster enclosures, undated (Box 73)
    - Dwight, Ill., 1950s (Box 73)
    - First National Bank, undated (Box 73)
    - Good copy, undated (Box 73)
    - Grass in the cracks, undated (Box 73)
    - Hoopeston Poster Advertising, undated (Box 73)
    - Hotel/Motel, undated (Box 73)
    - Junky looking outdoor signs, undated (Box 73)
    - Key Outdoor, undated (Box 73)
    - Landscaping, undated; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Lincoln Square, undated (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-2000 and undated; 9 folders (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-2000 and undated; 8 folders (Box 74)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Murray's pictures, undated (Box 75)
    - Neil & Green, Champaign, 1959 (Box 75)
    - New Mexico, 1994 (Box 75)
    - Newspapers, undated (Box 75)
    - Old photographs, undated; 3 folders (Box 75)
    - Old photographs, 1940s-1950s and undated; 4 folders (Box 76)
    - Old photographs--Buildings, 1940s (Box 76)
    - Old Royse, 1960s (Box 76)
    - On-Premise, undated (Box 76)
    - On-Premise corridors, undated (Box 76)
    - Photo album, 1967-1970; 2 folders (Box 76)
    - Political, undated (Box 76)
    - Radio stations, undated (Box 76)
    - Railroad leasings, 1936-1947 (Box 77)
    - Religion, undated (Box 77)
    - Remodeling, undated (Box 77)
    - Restaurants, undated (Box 77)
    - Robeson's, undated (Box 77)
    - San Diego, undated (Box 77)
    - Sears, undated (Box 77)
    - Skirting, undated (Box 77)
    - Small towns in Illinois, 1948 (Box 77)
    - The Fun is Back, undated (Box 77)
    - Unipole signs, undated; 3 folders (Box 77)
    - Urbana Pure Milk, undated (Box 77)
    - W. Lewis & Co., undated (Box 77)
    - Wandell's/Prairie Gardens, undated (Box 77)
    - War Bonds (WWII) Champaign, circa 1942 (Box 77)
  - Negatives, 1985-1988 and undated; 14
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-1988 and undated (Box 78)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 6 folders (Box 79)
- Ledgers and Minute Books, 1912-1982; 9
  - General Files, 1912-1982; 15
    - C&U--Cash books, 1924-1938 (Box 80)
    - C&U--Cash books, 1929-1943 (Box 81)
    - C&U--Cash books, 1943-1952 (Box 82)
    - C&U--Cash books, 1953-1959 (Box 83)
    - C&U--Cash books, 1960-1967 (Box 84)
    - C&U--Cash books, 1968-1974 (Box 85)
    - C&U--Cash books, 1975-1982 (Box 86)
    - C&U--Cash books, 1940-1946 (Box 93)
    - C&U--Contract Record, 1962-1963, 1975-1977 (Box 87)
    - C&U--Contract Record, 1947, 1970-1973 (Box 88)
    - C&U--General ledgers, 1924-1964 (Box 89)
    - C&U--General ledgers, 1925-1946 (Box 92)
    - C&U--Ground rent, 1950-1980s (Box 93)
    - C&U--Minutes, 1912 (Box 94)
    - C&U--Poster and production income, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 92)
    - C&U--Posting ledgers, 1932-1939 (Box 90)
    - C&U--Posting ledgers, 1940-1947 (Box 91)
    - C&U--Posting ledgers, 1930-1944 (Box 93)
    - C&U--Posting ledgers, 1969-1971 (Box 94)
    - C&U--Receipt book, 1970-1979 (Box 92)
    - C&U--Rentals, 1956-1974 (Box 94)
    - C&U--Stock certificate book, 1950s (Box 94)
    - C&U--Trial balance, 1945-1946 (Box 92)
    - Hoopeston Poster Advertising--Cash book, 1929-1943 (Box 95)
    - Hoopeston Poster Advertising--Day book, 1943-1948 (Box 95)
    - Hoopeston Poster Advertising--Expenses, 1938-1944 (Box 95)
    - Hoopeston Poster Advertising--Ledgers, 1929-1955 (Box 96)
    - Hoopeston Poster Advertising--Trial balance, 1938-1946 (Box 95)
- Oversize Materials, 1959-1992 and undated; 10
  - General Files, 1969-1990; 16
    - Billboard location map, 1982 (Box 97)
    - Champaign zoning map, 1984 (Box 97)
    - Champaign zoning map, 1980-1990 and undated; 3 folders (Box 98)
    - Route book sheets, 1969-1974; 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Traffic count map, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Urbana zoning map, 1980 (Box 98)
    - Urbana zoning map, 1989 (Box 97)
  - Legal Files, 1959-1979; 17
    - Champaign building permits, 1960 (Box 97)
    - Champaign zoning map, 1965 (Box 97)
    - Ernest E. Blanch Consultants exhibits, 1979 (Box 97)
    - Scrolled exhibit documents (Posting lists in Champaign and Urbana), 1959-1976 (Box 102)
    - Sign ordinance clippings, 1970 (Box 97)
  - OAAII, 1973-1992 and undated; 18
    - Exhibits for presentation on billboard design, landscaping, awards, undated; 4 folders (Box 99)
    - HACA maps, 1973-1992 (Box 99)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1994-2001; 11
  - General Files, 1994-2001; 19
    - City of Champaign study session 2001 May 22. VHS. TRT: 2:50 (Box 100)
    - Kip Pope advertising class 1994 Feb. VHS. (Box 100)
    - The Changing Faces of Outdoor Y2K South Africa. CD-R compact disc., 1999 (Box 100)
    - C&U logo, artwork for publications. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Miscellaneous folders. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Miscellaneous folders. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Monticello boards. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Report of Activities files. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Trash folder. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Report, new pages. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Kip Pope--Aesthetics 1 small files. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Kip Pope--Aesthetics 2 images and large files. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Kip Pope--Images from aesthetic articles disk 1. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Kip Pope--Images from aesthetic articles disk 2. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Kip Pope--Images from aesthetic articles disk 3. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Kip Pope--Municipal League text of remarks 3.5 floppy disc, 1999 (Box 101)
    - Mavica--Monticello boards and other billboards 3.5 floppy disk, 2001 (Box 101)
    - Old Hoopeston photographs. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Old Hoopeston photographs 1 of 3. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Old Hoopeston photographs 2 of 3. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Old Hoopeston photographs 3 of 3. ZIP disk, undated (Box 101)
    - Unidentified. ZIP Disk, undated (Box 101)
- Digital Files, 1999-2001 and undated; 12